(Stuart:)But I am ready to be helpful.
(Stuart:)In fact...
(Stuart:)I'm gonna go vacuum.
(Bernadette:)Hmm. Actually I just
did that this morning.
(Stuart:)Okay.
(Stuart:)Then I'll dust.
(Bernadette:)I did that, too.
(Stuart:)Then I'll check the batteries
in the smoke detectors.
(Bernadette:)Howard just did that.
(Howard:)Yeah, let him do it.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Remember when we got this
(Sheldon:)at Comic-Con?
(Stuart:)Oh, yeah.
(Leonard:)The Mr. Spock cuckoo clock.
(Mr Spock Cuckoo Clock:)Live long and prosper.
Live long and prosper.
(Mr Spock Cuckoo Clock:)Live long
and prosper.
(Mr Spock Cuckoo Clock:)Live long and prosper.
(Sheldon:)It's one of a kind.
(Penny:)So if it breaks
there'd be none of it?
(Sheldon:)Well, Leonard,
(Sheldon:)you know, who should keep this?
(Sheldon:)On the one hand, I love
Mr. Spock more than you do.
(Sheldon:)On the other hand, I care more
about clocks than you do.
(Leonard:)So you think you should keep it?